famous-smoke.com 2015-06-29

# Help Privacy | Famous Smoke Shop

Famous Smoke Shop is dedicated to earning your business as well as your trust. To that end, we hold your privacy in highest regard, and we promise not to sell, share, or rent your information, except as outlined in this privacy policy. By visiting the Famous Smoke Shop website, you agree to the practices described in this privacy policy. Please take a moment to read it over. Should you ever have any questions regarding the policies set forth here, please call us at 1-800-564-2486, or email [customerservice@famous-smoke.com](mailto:customerservice@famous-smoke.com).

Updating your personal information

You may either update your personal information by logging into the Famous Smoke Shop website, then accessing the My Account page, or by calling customer service at 1-800-564-2486.

Updates to Famous Smoke Shop policies

Famous Smoke Shop reserves the right to notify its customers of changes to its privacy policy, or other policies, as it sees fit.

Opting Out

Should you wish, at any time, and for any reason, to no longer receive communications from Famous Smoke Shop, you may either update your preferences by logging into the Famous Smoke Shop website, then accessing the My Account page, or by calling customer service at 1-800-564-2486.

Cookies

Cookies are useful in identifying how a customer arrived at the Famous Smoke Shop website, and allow us to further enhance your experience with us online. While browsing Famous Smoke Shop's websites, cookies identify you and keep track of your shopping cart. Please note: Cookies, by design, do not contain any sensitive information, such as credit card details. They are stored locally on your computer, and are only read by Famous Smoke Shop.

Does Famous collect my information?

In a word: yes. Any information you enter on our website, or provide us in any other way, is collected and stored in a secure environment. You are free to abstain from providing us certain information; this may, however, severely limit your online experience with Famous Smoke Shop. 

What information does Famous collect?

We collect billing, shipping and contact information, including email address and phone number. This allows us to process your order.

This information is transmitted securely, and cannot be viewed or recorded by others. Your credit card details are only shared with our bank; this is for authorization purposes. 

Why does Famous collect my information?

We strive to continuously improve the Famous Smoke Shop customer experience. This means, among other things, making site navigation easier, quicker, and more precise, ensuring accuracy in the processing and fulfillment of your orders, and earning your repeat business with fair prices and outstanding customer service. In short: we want to tailor-make a totally satisfying experience, and collecting your information is integral to achieving this goal.

How does Famous collect my information?

During the account creation process, and again when completing an order, you must provide your contact, billing, and shipping details. This information is used to complete your order, as well as to contact you regarding your order.

How does Famous use the information collected?

  1. Email: If you've opted to receive Famous Smoke Shop's weekly emails, we will send exclusive, money-saving specials directly to your inbox. If you would rather not receive these emails, or pick and choose which you would like to receive, then please visit the My Email Preferences page and update your preferences accordingly, or contact customer service at 1-800-564-2486. 

Additionally, we use your email address to send order confirmation emails and invoices. 

  2. Catalog: Since you have shown an interest in Famous Smoke Shop's products, you may begin to receive printed catalogs from us. If you no longer wish to receive these catalogs, please update your preferences accordingly on the My Account page, or contact customer service at 1-800-564-2486 if you don't have an online account. 
  3. Third Parties: Famous Smoke Shop works with certain third party companies that offer products and services cigar smokers may be interested in. If you purchase a product from us, it's possible that we may exchange your name with one or more of these companies. If you prefer to not have your name exchanged, you may update your preferences on the My Account page at any time, or contact customer service at 1-800-564-2486. 

Your Security

Famous Smoke Shop is dedicated to safeguarding your private information. We have many systems and procedures in place, each designed to protect your personal information from misuse.

During transmission, we employ Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software. This technology is an industry standard, encrypting all of your information, including credit card numbers, thus protecting your sensitive information as it is exchanged via the internet.

All of these efforts only prevent misuse and unauthorized access at Famous Smoke Shop's end. Therefore, if the security of your personal information is something you value, we must insist that you sign off and close all browsers when using a shared computer.
